

Summary

I'm Pourya Dehghan a Software engineer with the background of petrochemical engineering educations and designing experience. I started my coding journey two years ago, I feel really lucky that my job is my biggest hobby. I'm eager to make the leap and continue refining my skills with the right company.

Skills

HTML, CSS
JavaScript, Python
React, React Native, Boostrap
Django, MongoDB, PostgreSQL,
Github, Docker
Photoshop, Lightroom

Education and Training

Certificated

General Assembly Remote Software Engineer , 08/2021

Bachelor of Science

Marvdasht Azad University Petrochemical Engineer, 2013

Languages

English

Persian

Turkish

Experience

General Assembly

Software Engineer | Remote 05/2021 to 08/2021

- Learning programming and computer science fundamentals, and creating full stack applications.
- Feature Projects:

Denj-This is a full stack mobile application that I created with React Native. This application is about cozy places that users have been and they want to share with other people.

Agora-This is the full stack application that we created as a group. This is an online application for discussions on a forum based on topics and descriptions. Each forum has their own and is fully functional.

Dota2 Heroes-My App is called Dota2 Heroes. It's an app that shows the all Dota2 Heroes and if you click on hero it gives you the detail and attributes of that hero.

Dota2_Simon-This is a Simon game which players must repeat random sequences of by clicking the buttons in correct order. The differences between this game and the other Simon games are that I used the Dota 2 character's images and sounds to make it more interesting.

Uber

Driver | Atlanta, GA 04/2017 to 06/2021 Provided excellent customer service to patrons Interacted with riders.

Yerce Köşk

Photo Editor & Designer | Turkey 06/2014 to 12/2016 Photography company specializing in wedding photos and albums.

Designed and created wedding albums for customers.

Websites, Portfolios, Profiles

- https://www.pouryadegan.com
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/degan90
- https://github.com/Degan90